thrashermagazine.com 2014-06-26

# Thrasher Skateboard Magazine | Privacy Policy

_Updated: January 29th, 2014_

Welcome to ThrasherMagazine.com, a Website created by High Speed Productions, Inc., (“High Speed Productions,” “We,” “Us”) which lives at ThrasherMagazine.com (“Thrasher Magazine,” “Website,” “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to any information that is collected while you are on the Site and our webstore at Shop.ThrasherMagazine.com. Our goal with this policy is to be transparent about the information we collect, how we use it, and how it is shared.

This Privacy Policy is part of our [Terms & Conditions](http://www.thrashermagazine.com/user-help/terms-conditions/), and by using the Site you agree to both. 

 **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

1\. We collect limited information when you browse the site

When you visit the Site we collect log data, for example: the type of browser and operating system you are using, the address of the external or internal page that referred you, your IP address and pages on the site that you visit in association with your IP address. This information is recorded even if you do not have a registered ThrasherMagazine.com account, or even when you are logged out of your account. We mostly use this information to diagnose issues with the site.

2\. We Collect Information Using Cookies

Advertising pays our bills so we use a lot of cookies. You should know how [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) work. You should support [cookie reform efforts](http://donottrack.us/) if you choose.

3\. We Collect Information When You Sign Up For The ThrasherMagazine.com Email Blast

When you subscribe to receive the ThrasherMagazine.com Email Blast, we require your email address. It is optional to provide your first and/or last name and we only use it to personalize the message. We do not use your email for any other purpose than to send the Blast. You will remain on this list until you unsubscribe, which you can do at any time. We partner with Constant Contact to provide email list services. Their privacy policy can be found [here](http://www.constantcontact.com/security).

4\. We Collect Information When You Communicate With Us Directly

If you email us or send other communications to us directly, we will retain your email or address and correspondence so that we may respond to your request. We retain this information indefinitely so that we have a history of our past communications.

 **WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**

It is our policy not to share or sell your personally identifiable information with any third party. We may, however, share information under the following circumstances:

1\. If we receive your informed consent;

2\. If it is necessary for a third party provider to perform tasks on our behalf (as described in this policy);

3\. If we believe doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or valid legal process. If we are going to release your information, we will do our best to provide you with notice in advance, if we have a means to contact you, unless we are prohibited by court order from doing so.

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

It should go without saying, but we'll say it anyway: this website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, unless we have specified them in this document.

 **DATA SECURITY**

We have adopted commercially reasonable technical, physical and administrative procedures to protect the confidentiality of the information that we collect on our site. However, the Internet is not a vault and data can be lost.

 **INTERNATIONAL VISITORS**

High Speed Productions, Inc. is a San Francisco, California-based company whose servers are housed in the USA. All personal information we collect from our international users is processed according to US law.

 **RATED PG-13**

We have kids. We love kids.  Really we do. But the United States government has put limits on our ability to accept users under a certain age through the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm). So to be clear, ThrasherMagazine.com is not intended for users under the age of 13. Nobody under 13 may create an account or use any part of the Site that requires the submission of personally identifiable information, like email or name. Any account that is created by a person under 13 will be terminated and any content created will be removed from the Site.

 **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may be revised. If we make material changes to this policy, we will make them available on ThrasherMagazine.com.

 **CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or your information, please email our webmaster: greg@thrashermagazine.com

 **COOKIE POLICY**

We use a lot of cookies on this site. Online publishing is primarily supported by advertising and so is ThrasherMagazine.com. Until there’s a better way, we’re stuck with cookies, all of us. What we can do, however, is inform you about the cookies that we use and how you can opt-out from using them, if you choose. Just remember, cookies power the advertising and the advertising pays for the Site.

What is a cookie?

Cookies are small data files that websites store in your hard drive. They create a unique id that is associated with your browser. We use first-party cookies for analytics, which tell us about user activity on our site. We use third-party cookies to collect information about your habits across multiple sites and to provide advertising that is targeted to your interests. Our third-party advertising partners also use third-party cookies. More information about each is provided below.

 **Analytics, Advertising, & Social Media Cookies**

As always, no personally identifiable information will be collected.

1\. Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how you engage with our site so that we can improve it. Google Analytics reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You may install a Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Button [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB). The Google Analytics Privacy Policy can be read [here](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

2\. Google Ad Products

We use Google Ads products like DoubleClick for Publishers. You can adjust Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). You may [permanently opt-out of the Google DoubleClick cookie here](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/plugin?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCioEXDOsPa8IjFdovMgXR52Z5_ciapDi9aBWF0NP4jQPppY2BYJ0IF3-9zV8zkLxemICvwX7L3h5ApQjk02fG-GqJA3LBQ-u7bXYoVk29_PY_6RVccjpcEvV0INuRfbuOykw-5OSkZre8NH3RNGVMefp2YkLwnH0YhSrC9tqVGmtFxvDk0).

3\. Social Media Widgets

We display sharing buttons so you can use social networking to share items from our site.

This includes the Facebook recommend button and other interactive mini-programs that run on our site that collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and sets a cookie to enable the widget to function properly. Your interactions with these Widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them, not by this Privacy Policy.

 **More Advertising Disclosures**

Just so we are clear about how we use advertising on the site, below are some of the most common kinds of sponsorships on ThrasherMagazine.com:

1\. Sponsored sections, themes, or categories: An advertising partner sometimes sponsors a category, section, or series of posts within a particular theme.  Of course, the sponsor won't have any editorial input, guidance, or approval, of the content of our posts.

2\. Sponsored videos: An advertising partner sponsors a series of videos on a particular theme or over a given time period. That sponsorship may include interstitial or embedded ads within the video and/or branding of the video player. Sponsors have no control over the editorial content. 

3\. Contests: A marketer may sponsor a contest on the site. We hope you win!

4\. Traditional banner ads: We have strict guidelines on the banner advertisements that we accept. Animated ads can't be longer than 30 seconds. Audio must be user-initiated. And of course, no pop-ups or pop-unders. Unfortunately, ads that break those rules sometimes do slip through our automated system. So if you see a banner ad that violates this policy, please let us know by emailing  [our ad department](mailto:mike@hsproductions.com) and we'll investigate.
